# **Ajithkumar**

9790798440 ajithajith486809@gmail.com

Result oriented Internet / E-Commerce professional. I have been working in the Customer Care Executive (Call Centre) for more than 8 years. Currently I am working as a Ajithkumar at Customer service. I have extensive experience in areas of Government Procurement, Government Securities, Traditional Ira

### **Experience**

Customer service
Jun 2021 - Present

Customer service

Jun 2021 - Present

Customer service

Jun 2021 - Present

Customer service

Jun 2021 - Present

Customer service

Jun 2021 - Present

Customer service

Jun 2021 - Present

Customer service

Jun 2021 - Present

Customer service

Jun 2021 - Present

Customer service

Jun 2021 - Present

Customer service

Jun 2021 - Present

Customer service

Jun 2021 - Present

Customer service

Jun 2021 - Present

Customer service

Jun 2021 - Present

Customer service

Jun 2021 - Present

Customer service

Jun 2021 - Present

Customer service

Jun 2021 - Present

Customer service

Jun 2021 - Present

Customer service

Jun 2021 - Present

Customer service

Jun 2021 - Present

Customer service
Jun 2021 - Present

Customer service
Jun 2021 - Present

Customer service
Jun 2021 - Present

Customer service
Jun 2021 - Present

Customer service
Jun 2021 - Present

Customer service
Jun 2021 - Present

Customer service
Jun 2021 - Present

Customer service
Jun 2021 - Present

Customer service
Jun 2021 - Present

Customer service
Jun 2021 - Present

Customer service
Jun 2021 - Present

Customer service
Jun 2021 - Present

Customer service
Jun 2021 - Present

Customer service
Jun 2021 - Present

Customer service Jun 2021 - Present

Customer service
Jun 2021 - Present

Customer service
Jun 2021 - Present

Customer service Jun 2021 - Present

Customer service Jun 2021 - Present

Customer service Jun 2021 - Present

Customer service
Jun 2021 - Present

Customer service
Jun 2021 - Present

Customer service Jun 2021 - Present Customer service
Jun 2021 - Present

Customer service

Jun 2021 - Present

Customer service

Jun 2021 - Present

Customer service

Jun 2021 - Present

Customer service

Jun 2021 - Present

Customer service

Jun 2021 - Present

Customer service

Jun 2021 - Present

Customer service

Jun 2021 - Present

Customer service

Jun 2021 - Present

Customer service

Jun 2021 - Present

Customer service

Jun 2021 - Present

Customer service

Jun 2021 - Present

Customer service

Jun 2021 - Present

Customer service

Jun 2021 - Present

Customer service

Jun 2021 - Present

Customer service

Jun 2021 - Present

Customer service

Jun 2021 - Present

## **Education**

B.A

B.A English 2014

### Skills

Government Procurement, Government Securities, Traditional Ira

# Other Information

Largest Team Size Handled: Notice Period: **3 months**